utah3d.net 2018-07-10

# Travel Scenic Utah In 3D Panoramas | Utah3D.Net | Privacy Policy | Utah3d.net

WILDERNESS PHOTOGRAPHER, MARTIN VAN HEMERT • PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY

Privacy Policy

Life changes, the web and the way we use it changes, and this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Please check back to learn of any changes that we make.

This Privacy Policy covers our websites. We have links on our sites to other sites that provide products or services we feel are useful. We deal with various third party providers of certain services. We strive to deal with reputable firms and individuals. We cannot, however make any claims regarding the privacy policies of other websites, and we recommend you check these other sites for information you might need.

Personal Information

You do not need to provide any personal information to visit and enjoy the Utah3D.Net or vanhemert.com websites. Should you choose to purchase products or services we offer, we obviously will need pertinent information to fill your request, which could include information such as email addresses, mailing addresses, names, and phone numbers. This information may also be recorded and stored by firms providing third party services for us. Record is kept of email addresses of those choosing to email us or post blog comments. This information will not be given to any other parties, other than those in the act of providing necessary third party services (for example, common carriers will need your address to deliver an item you have ordered, and FeedBlitz will store your email address to send our email updates).

Bank/Credit Card Information

At this time, we are using PayPal to handle transactions involving the exchange of funds. We also accept direct payment by check. We do not keep any bank or credit card account information on our servers. This information will only be recorded by PayPal and our receiving bank as they normally would in the course of their business.

Other Information Recorded and Stored

As is true with most websites, we, our third party service providers, our marketing affiliates, and those who have links on our websites, use technologies including, but not limited to, cookies, DART cookies, and Web beacons to gather information regarding your IP Address, the browser you use, and information about how you navigate through our/their sites. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages, and some of the sites we have links to use cookies and these other technologies as well. Cookies can be deleted or blocked by the user. They do not contain personally identifying information. For a detailed explanation of many of these technologies, visit this link.

Privacy Policy

©2011, Martin van Hemert - All rights reserved.
